The most important thing is there?.
The reason why I'm here
is that I'll protect you!.
It's okay, let's go ahead and move on!.
The moon will always come to the moon?.
The moon will come to the moon!.
Let's look at the moon?.
Whew, good, safe and sound.
Yeah, that wore me out, huh?
Safe and sound, my butt,
I thought I was gonna die!
What was I supposed to do?
You were the one who said we couldn't
use the elevator because we'd get caught.
I didn't have a choice.
This doesn't mean, hey,
let's jump down, idiot.
You can't slide around like
that square-knocked ship right.
Got it? Right.
Sorry about that.
Whatever.
It's fine since we're safe now.
Then stop hitting me.
However, we might not be safe for long.
We won't. Why not? What's wrong?
This island's topography and climate.
With this much wind blowing and the
atmospheric pressure falling so rapidly,
there's likely going to
be a typhoon here tonight.
This place is called the City of Water.
Think about it.
Its greatest weakness
would have to be flooding.
Okay, so it floods. So what?
Well, it worries me, that's all.
I'll check into it later.
Come on, let's head back to
the inn for the time being.
In compliance with the
Aqua Laguna warning that
was issued for the entire
island earlier today.
All docks on the shipbuilding
island are now to be
considered public shelter
and evacuation centers.
Large crowds are expected, so please
take shelter as quickly as possible.
Additionally, keep in mind that Dock
1 is currently in a dangerous state.
Alright, I'll put the iron board on.
Hey honey, you sure we
have everything we'll need?
Yes.
Now come on, we need to take
shelter in the shipyard.
Patience, patience.
You gotta be careful sealing this board
if the inside of our house gets flooded,
everything will be ruined.
Hey, the wind is starting to pick up.
The waves will be here anytime now. Hurry.
If we take too long, those assassin
pirates are gonna show up too. What?
Where'd he disappear to
I'm sure he went this way.
He's gotta be around here.
Okay, you guys look over there, right?
Hell is going on are they
chasing me I don't understand?
Wait a sec is this why
everyone's chasing after
me culprits in the
assassination plot well that
Sucks can't go back to
the inn now I'll be out in
the open hey who goes there
who are you over here?
There's a suspicious guy
hiding in the alley you
sure about this there's
no mistake I'm certain.
They've been staying here at the inn
since they checked in last night.
They took off just a little while ago.
They're staying here?
Yes, that's right.
They still have lots of
luggage left in their room.
I'm sure they'll be back for it sometime.
Right.
You guys stay here, okay?
The rest of you search the
surrounding area with me.
Look sharp.
Leave no stone unturned.
Does everybody got it?
Huh.
No one's here.
Are you 100 % certain
that this is their ship?
There's no mistaking it.
Look up there.
That's the flag of the Straw Hat Pirates.
They probably already abandoned her.
She's all worn out.
Did you find them?
No, they're gone.
There's not much left on board.
Pretty sure she was
abandoned and left to sink.
Let's keep looking around.
Who were those guys?
Is there something going on in the city?
Find anything?
Not a trace of them.
Damn it!
Where are they?
They sure are persistent.
Hey, Luffy?
Huh?
What is it, Nami?
Do you think everybody's okay?
These guys are all over the place.
Chopper and Sanji are probably safe because
no one knows their faces yet, but still.
Come on, we need to hurry.
Right.
It looks like the C-Train's
still in operation.
I guess the noon departure
has already left.
There's another one scheduled for
tonight, even in all this bad weather.
The 11 p .m., leaving for Annie's lobby.
That Sea Train is pretty impressive.
Hey, any news on those pirates?
We've got nothing.
If we can capture just one of those
three from the wanted posters,
we'll make them cough
up who the others are.
Hurry, before the waves get too high.
Maybe we can't find Robin
because she got on the Sea Train.
Well, if she did, that would make
things worse than they already are.
Water 7's too big an
area to cover on its own.
What if...
what if I did something to
upset her back at the bookstore?
Don't be ridiculous.
No way that's the reason.
Hey, excuse me.
Have you seen a beautiful woman
who kind of looks like this?
You mean the one who's about 20
years older than that picture?
If I had, I would have told the newspapers
or the galley law company about it.
To think she's an assassin.
Kind of shocking, huh?
Huh?
I admire you for trying to
track down that criminal,
but I suggest you find
yourself some shelter soon.
Aqua Laguna is on its
way. Ha ha ha. Take care.
Things are getting dangerous around here.
What about the others?
Think they're okay?
I'm sure Luffy's fine.
Nami's the one that I'm really
worried about right now.
At any rate, this city's
becoming quite the ghost town.
The wind's really picking up.
I'm sure most people are
already in the shelter.
Where could she be?
Hey, Robin!
Where are you?
That scent, is it...
Huh?
Chopper, what is it? Chopper!
Hey, wait for me!
This way.
Hey, Chopper! Chopper!
Are you all right?
Chopper, did you hurt yourself?
There you are.
You can't just go running off like that.
What the hell's the matter with you?
One second, you're right beside me.
It's Robin!
Robin!
Where in the world have you been?
Everyone's worried.
We've been looking everywhere for you.
Come on, let's head back to the inn.
A lot's happened while you were gone.
I'll explain everything on the way.
This damn water split us up.
Hold on.
I'll find another way over there.
Don't bother. It's all right.
Stay where you are.
There's no need.
Indeed, because I won't be
coming back to you and your crew.
We're parting ways, here, in this city.
What the...
what in the world are you talking about?
Oh, wait, you mean the stuff they
said about you in the newspaper?
Don't worry about it.
None of us believes it.
Pirates are falsely accused
of crimes all the time.
We're easy targets.
About that.
I apologize for pinning such an
unreasonable crime on all of you.
But as far as my involvement, everything
that was said in the newspaper is true.
Late last night, I broke into the
mayor's place of residence and shot him.
No way.
Inside me, I carry a darkness
that none of you know about.
One day, that darkness will
be the end of all of you.
Every organization that
she's had something
to do with in the past
has been annihilated.
Not one single solitary
member escaped except for her.
I'm afraid you'll be taking the fall
for last night's attack while I escape.
And let me warn you, the
situation will only get worse.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand!
Why I'm doing it, there's no
need for you to understand.
Robin!
What happened?
You're not making any sense!
This isn't like you at all!
Please!
We'll work this out together!
Although I only spent a short time
with you, from this day forward,
we will never see each other again.
Thank you for all of the
kindness you've shown me.
Know that I'll never forget it.
Goodbye.
Wait!
No!
Please!
This can't...
This can't be happening!
Hey!
Come back!
Stop!
You don't know what you're saying, Robin!
Wait! Please! Come back!
I lost track of her scent. I see.
Hey, Chopper.
Go meet up with Luffy
and the others and tell
them everything that happened
between us and Robin.
I don't want you to
leave out a single word.
Sure.
As for me, let's just say I have a plan.
I'll try to be careful.
We'll meet up later.
Where'd they go?
Check the alleys!
You don't think they're
on the rooftops, do you?
Damn it, we lost them!
I don't get it.
I'm sure they went this way.
We better keep moving.
All right, but we should check
inside the buildings, too.
Good!
We'll split up.
Let's go! Yeah!
Is it okay now? Wait a sec.
Where did you last see them?
Just a little longer.
Hmm?
What? Stop!
I'm begging you.
Are you crazy?
I got to evacuate.
Stop pestering me.
Come on.
I have money, okay?
Here, take it.
I need as much lumber, tar,
and rope as this will buy.
Oh, and also some nails, latches,
and tin plates, if you don't mind.
I said I'm closing the shop.
It'll just take a second. Please.
Okay, kid, but I'm afraid this
money ain't gonna buy much for you.
Uh, then how about I sell my tools?
Will that make up for the rest?
Hey, hey, come on, stop it.
We don't do barter.
This is the big city, you know.
I'm sorry, but it's cash only.
You win, but let's make it quick.
You sure you're okay
carrying that with all those
injuries can't you get some
friends to help you out?
Hey I knew this was a bad idea!
Wait this isn't gonna work.
I'm fine.
I got it.
This is nothing.
Don't worry I can do it. No look.
Here take these.
You're hungry, right?
Thank you.
Sure thing!
Try to be careful.
Good luck out there, kid.
Mmm.
These are good.
Really good.
Guess that guy was pretty nice after all.
The waves sure are
getting high, aren't they?
Don't worry, Mary.
You're going to be just fine.
After all, you flew in the sky, remember?
You got nothing to be afraid of.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's got you riled up, big guy?
Come on, Franky, you can tell us.
What's up, bro?
I got so much rage inside me, I feel
another rampage coming on right about now!
Hey, wait for me, bro,
don't rampage alone!
As always, thanks for the drinks, Blueno!
What got into him all of a sudden?
Is there something going on?
It's me.
Never can tell with that guy.
Only idiots know what idiots are thinking.
Looks like the crowd cleared out.
Yeah, no thanks to you.
I'll have you know that Luffy and I
had a perfectly good hiding place.
Until you led that angry
mob straight to us.
Like I said, with that
many people looking.
They were going to find you anyway.
Oh yeah, that reminds me.
How'd you know we were
down there, Chopper?
Your smell?
Ah, should have known But
wait, wasn't Sanji with you?
Well, he was
No way!
That doesn't make any sense!
Did Robin really say that to you?
We were prepared for this, weren't we?
After all, Robin was our enemy
before we let her join the crew.
This might be our only chance to find
out the truth, so we shouldn't run away.
There's still a lot of things
we don't know about Robin.
Now it's time to decide if
she's a friend or a foe.
The situation will get worse.
From this day forward, we
will never see each other.
You're sure?
That's all she said, Chopper?
If she says she won't see us after
today and things are gonna get worse,
maybe that means the attack
on Iceberg was just a warm
-up and she has something even
bigger planned for tonight.
I don't know why Robin's
doing any of this,
so it's hard to make a guess
as to what she's planning!
But seeing how much commotion her
first attack on the mayor caused,
there's only one way to make things
worse in other words she'll murder him
I think that's what she's
trying to tell us at least
Also since she told Chopper that
she'll be pinning the crime on us,
it could be that she's
feeding us all these little
hints to try and lure us out
to the crime scene tonight?
Think so?
If that is her plan, it would be convenient
for her if we did happen to show up,
since that would put us
at the scene of the crime.
You say you don't know
what she's thinking,
but it sounds to me like you've
already decided that she's our enemy.
I'm talking about
possibilities here, that's all.
We should always be prepared for
the worst-case scenario, understand?
If I get locked into a single line
of thinking, it'll only slow me down.
If she's my friend, I have
to be ready to forgive.
But if she's my enemy, I
have to be ready to fight.
Our best chance to settle this is
tonight are we going of course?
It's not that I object
to the plan but we're
still forgetting something
Sanji said he saw.
Robin walking with
someone in a mask remember
obviously that wasn't one of
us but Iceberg said exactly
the same thing that he
was attacked by Robin and
a large man in a mask
that he didn't recognize.
Whoever he is I bet he's the reason
Robin is doing all of this stuff.
Yeah that means it isn't our
fault and we just need to
beat the real bad guy right
that's the ideal situation.
But on the other hand it's also possible
that this guy is one of Robin's friends.
The problem is we don't have much to
go on other than a big man in a mask.
So where do we even start I mean
what is our goal here we find
Robin and capture her that's the
only way we'll ever know the truth.
You're right, we're wasting time
here trying to figure it out.
Just one thing, Robin
won't be easy to catch.
After all,
the world government's been trying for
20 years and it still hasn't happened.
Like he said, it's the only
way we'll really know for sure.
Yeah, let's settle this right now!
Right.
Come on, Galilaw's waiting.
Damn, it's late.
Where'd that Straw Hat run off to?
Paulie, we gotta go.
All these streets are
gonna flood before long.
All right, let's head back.
I'm going to the main office.
Sounds good, boss.
You heard him, guys.
Time to move out.
Get out here and find me, Straw Hat!
Where are you?
Stop hiding!
I thought that little turd had some
backbone, but I guess I was wrong.
Won't even show his face.
I know what you're saying,
bro, but to be fair, the whole island
is hunting him down right now, you know?
Exactly.
I bet he's hiding if he
hasn't been caught already.
By the way, what's with this weird
crab walk thing all of a sudden?
If we face the front, then the wind
catches our hair, and we blow away!
Speaking of which, the weather isn't the
only thing that's out of control today.
Tell me about it.
It's like you've got a rampage
going on inside you, too.
Shut up.
I'm just like that this week, okay?
Hey, Ro!
Hey, it's Ro! Hey, Ro!
Well, if it isn't, Samba.
Tell me!
Tell me that you beat up
those stupid Straw Hats!
Yeah, but I tried to.
Some angry mops showed up, got
in the way, then Luffy took off.
Are those guys lucky or what?
When you're on a rampage, nobody survives.
That's weird.
I wondered why that weak dude with the
long nose was fixing the ship on his own.
I figured that you'd wrecked
up the rest of the crew so
bad that he was the only one
left who could do anything.
Wait, you found one of them?
Yeah, on their ship.
Well, that's just fine,
because all we need is one.
In other words, we'll use that loser
as bait to lure out the rest of them.
Whoa, bro's got his bad guy face on, guys!
All right, you good-for-nuffins.
I want you to march through the
town and spread the word for me.
Say, we've got Longnose, and if you
don't want him swimming with the fishes?
then come to the warehouse
under the bridge.
Tell him Franky sent ya.
In the meantime, I'll go nab Longnose so
we can make good on our little threat.
You get it, bro!
I swear we won't let you down!
Aqua Laguna is coming for you!
Here comes a big wave!
So, do you know what's going
on with those Straw Hats?
I'm not sure.
I don't think they've caught them yet.
Still on the loose.
That's no good.
And with everyone so
worked up about the storm,
they'll have the perfect
chance to attack again.
And what I heard is that tonight?
All the craftsmen from
the Call Law Company.
and he will be guarding the main
office to protect the mayor.
Whoa!
That's a really big deal, isn't it?
How many people have the
Straw Hats got, anyway?
Some say 50, some say 100, or even more!
Remember, the captain's got
100 million bounty on his head.
For all we know,
he could be sending an army of 3,000 men
to fight the shipwrights as we speak!
Are you kidding?
That sounds really bad!
What are we gonna do?
All right, men, hold your formation
and don't give an inch. Yeah!
Don't even let a single fly
get through, got it? Yeah!
Bring it on!
What's wrong with you?
Would you please be quiet, Tile Stone?
I heard the Straw Hats weren't
spotted on the Sea Train.
That means they're still
here on the island somewhere.
Still,
they'd be complete idiots if they tried to
show up with all of these guards around.
Yeah, you'd think, but that didn't stop
the dumbass that barged in here earlier,
did it?
We gotta be ready for anything.
Well, this is reassuring,
but it's a bit much.
They wanted to do this for you.
I'm not royalty.
Pardon me, sir,
but why on earth did you put Nico
Robin's wanted poster up on your wall?
It bother you?
A bit.
It's better if you don't know.
That girl is a demon.
There sure are a lot of people out there.
It's a little far, too.
It'll be fine if you rocket
through the window, right?
After Robin shows up, I mean.
That's right.
If we make a commotion first,
then they'll just sneak in while
we're dealing with the guards.
Let's be patient.
Get ready!
Strike at anything that
moves, men! Got it? Yeah!